What the hell?
Goddamn son of a bitch...
Goddamn son of a...
What the hell?
Hey, my turn!
Me.
Come on.
Hey, what's wrong
with this picture?
Nice night for a walk, eh?
Nice night for a walk.
Washday tomorrow.
Nothing clean, right?
Nothing clean. Right.
I think this guy's a couple
cans short of a six-pack.
Your clothes.
Give them to me. Now.
Fuck you, asshole!
Hey, sugar, how about it?
I don't have to put up
with that bullshit, man.
She's always after me.
I don't... I don't...
Hey, buddy. Did you just
see a real bright light?
See that guy?
- Hold it right there!
- He's rabbiting.
- Hey! I said hold it!
- Go!
That son of a bitch took my pants!
- What day is it? The date!
- 12th... May. Thursday.
- What year?!
- What?
He's got my gun! Let's go!
3831, they lost the suspect.
Guard it for me, big buns.
- Hi.
- Hi. I'm late.
So am I.
- I'm in it.
- So am I.
Honey, could I have
that coffee now, please?
Yes, sir.
- OK, who gets the burly beef?
- Uh, I ordered barbecued beef.
- I think that's mine, but I didn't order fries.
- He gets the barbecued beef.
- Mine's the chili beef deluxe.
- OK, who gets the burly beef?
- Miss, we're ready to order now.
- Yes, ma'am.
Aah!
Oh, I'm so sorry. Oh, lord.
This isn't real leather, is it?
This special sucks.
Nice going, kid. Ought
to give you the tip.
Look at it this way... in a hundred
years, who's going to care?
The twelve-gauge auto-loader.
That's Italian. You
can go pump or auto.
The .45 long slide,
with laser sighting.
These are brand-new. We just
got them in. That's a good gun.
Just touch the trigger, the beam
comes on, and you put the red dot
where you want the bullet
to go. You can't miss.
Anything else?
A phased plasma rifle
in the 40-watt range.
Just what you see, pal.
The Uzi 9mm.
You know your weapons, buddy. Any one
of these is ideal for home defense.
So, uh... which will it be?
All.
I may close early today.
There's a 15-day wait on the handguns,
but the rifles you can take right now.
You can't do that.
Wrong.
Hi, baby. Yeah, yeah, it's me.
Listen, I need you to come pick
me up. My bike just broke down.
I don't care what you're doing.
Come and get me. What the...
Hey, man, you got a
serious attitude problem.
- Sarah Connor?
- Yes?
I'm on my break, Chuck.
Carla's got my station.
Sarah, come here!
It's about you. I mean, sort of.
It's so incredible. You're
not gonna believe this.
Sit down. You are
going to love this.
- Shh!
- What?
Has been compiled
from several witnesses.
Once again, Sarah Connor,
thirty-five, mother of two,
brutally shot to death
in her home this afternoon.
- You're dead, honey.
- In other late-breaking news,
teamster representatives
have issued a statement...
Yes, friends, if you're into
stereo and you're into sound,
for the greatest sound around you, come to
Bob's Stereo at 25000 Sepulveda Boulevard.
Yes, we've got woofers, tweeters, the newest
in digital audio and compact laser discs.
We've got graphic equalizers and sound
balancers that adjust the sound to fit...
Sorry.
Hello.
First, I'm gonna rip the buttons
off your blouse, one by one,
and then run my tongue down your
neck to your bare, gleaming breasts,
and then slowly, slowly pull
your jeans off... inch by inch.
Ginger, it's Matt!
And lick your belly in circles
further and further down,
and then pull your panties
off with my teeth.
Who is this?
I... I, uh... Sarah?
Oh, Jesus. I'm sorry.
I thought you were...
- Can I talk to Ginger, please?
- Sure, Bunky.
It's the creep.
Hello.
First, I'm gonna rip the buttons
off your blouse, one by one...
You fuckin' pigs! Wait till
I get my hands on you!
- Get off of me!
- Sit down, fella.
Ed.
- What do you got?
- Dead girl.
- I can see that.
- Sarah Ann Connor, secretary, 35,
shot six times at less than ten
feet. Large caliber weapon.
You know, these work.
What's this?
Dead girl 2, sent over from
Valley Division this afternoon.
- I'm sure there's a point to all of this.
- Look at the name, Ed.
Sarah Louise... Connor.
Is this right?
You're kidding me.
The press is going to be
short-stroking it all over the place.
A one-day pattern killer.
I hate the weird ones.
So...
Better than mortal man deserves.
- Ginger, have you seen Pugsley?
- No, not lately. Did you check messages?
Uh-uh. I thought you did.
Hi, Sarah, this is your mom...
There you are, young man.
- You mind your mother.
- So call me back, will you, dear? Uh, bye.
Hi, Sarah. Dan Moorski.
Uh, something's come up,
and it looks like I won't
be able to make it tonight.
Just can't get out of it. Look, I'm
really sorry. I'll make it up to you.
Call you in a day or so,
OK? Sorry. Bye.
That bum. So what if
he has a Porsche?
He can't treat you like this. It's
Friday night, for Christ's sake!
I'll live.
I'll break his kneecaps.
Well... Pugsley still loves
me, don't you, baby?
God. It's disgusting.
- I'm gonna go to a movie, kiddo.
- OK.
- You and Matt have a good time.
- We will. You, too.
OK.
Damn it, Matt!
Oh, shit.
Lieutenant, are you aware
that these two killings
occurred in the same order as
their listings in the phone book?
Now, what can I tell you
guys? No comment.
But, lieutenant, we've
got two murders...
- That coffee's two hours cold.
- Mm-hmm.
I put a cigarette out in it.
- Did you reach the next girl yet?
- No. I keep getting an answering machine.
- Send a unit.
- I sent a unit.
There's no answer at the door, and
the apartment manager's not home.
Call her.
- I just called her.
- Call her again.
Give me a cigarette.
Hi there.
Ha ha ha. Fooled you. You're talking to
a machine, but don't be shy, it's OK.
Same shit.
I can hear it now. He's gonna be called
the goddamn "Phone Book killer."
I hate these press cases,
especially the weird press cases.
- Where you going?
- To make a statement.
Maybe make these jackals
work for us for a change.
If I can get on the tube by eleven
o'clock, maybe she'll call us.
Well...
- How do I look?
- Like shit, boss.
Your mama.
Lieutenant!
This just in. Police have
announced the name of the victim
in the second of two execution-style
murders which took place today.
Incredibly, the names of the two
victims are virtually identical.
Two hours ago, 35-year-old Sarah Ann
Connor was pronounced dead at the scene
- in her Santa Monica apartment...
- Can we change this?
- Sure.
- Sarah Louise Connor was slain by an...
- Don't touch it!
- Unknown gunman earlier today in her home.
Now, police are refusing to speculate
on the apparent similarity
between these shooting deaths, and no
other connection between the two victims
has been established as of yet.
Of course, we'll have more on this
late-breaking story as it comes in.
A spectacular fire fueled by solvents,
oils, and other flammable liquids
swept through an oil company
on North Spring Street
just northeast of Chinatown
Wednesday night...
- Hey, you got a phone?
- It's in the back! Hey! 4.50.
You have reached the Los Angeles
Police Department emergency number.
All our lines are busy. If you
need a police car sent out to you,
please stay on the line.
2-11 in progress at Bob's Liquor,
corner of third and Cameron.
Pugsley, shoo! Go on. I'm going
to make a belt out of you.
Whoa!
Don't make me bust you up, man!
Hi there. Ha ha ha. Fooled you.
You're talking to a machine,
but don't be shy, it's OK.
Machines need love
too, so talk to it,
and Ginger, that's me, or
Sarah will get back to you.
Wait for the beep.
Ginger, this is Sarah!
Pick up if you're there!
I'm at this place on Pico Boulevard
called Technoir. I'm really scared.
I think that there's
somebody's after me.
Uh, I hope that you
play this back soon.
I need you and Matt to come and
pick me up as soon as possible.
The police keep transferring me around.
I'm gonna give them another try.
The number here is 555-9175.
Call me, kiddo. I need your help.
It's her.
- Sarah Connor? It's Lieutenant Traxler.
- Look, Lieutenant, don't put me on hold
- and don't transfer me to another department!
- Don't worry. I won't. Now, just relax.
- Can you tell me where you are?
- I'm in this bar called Technoir.
Yeah, I know. It's on Pico.
Are you all right?
Yeah, but I don't want to leave.
I think there's a guy following me.
All right, now, listen, Miss
Connor, now, listen carefully,
you're in a public place, so
you'll be safe till we get there,
but stay visible. Don't go outside
or even to the rest room.
- I'll have a car there in a hot minute.
- OK.
Hey, that guy didn't pay.
Come with me if you want to live.
Come on!
This is 1-L19. I got a
hit-and-run felony.
Suspect vehicle... late model gray
Ford, headed westbound on 7th.
He's really moving, punching
lights all the way.
I'm going to need an ambulance
at 7th and Broadway right now.
Hold it!
All units watch for a
late-model gray Ford,
last seen westbound
on 7th and Broadway.
Hold on.
Are you injured? Are you shot?
No!
Do exactly what I say. Exactly.
Don't move unless I say. Don't
make a sound unless I say.
Do you understand?
- Do you understand?!
- Yes! Yes! Please, don't hurt me.
I'm here to help you. I'm
Reese, Sergeant Techcom,
DN38416, assigned to protect you.
You've been targeted for termination.
Attempt to intercept, 1-L19.
This is 1-L19. Westbound on
Olympic approaching Overland.
This is a mistake.
I didn't do anything.
No, but you will. It's very
important that you live.
This isn't true. How could that
man just get up after you...
He's not a man. A machine.
A Terminator. A Cyberdine
systems model 101.
A machine?
- Like a robot?
- Not a robot. A cyborg.
A cybernetic organism.
- No. He was bleeding.
- Just a second.
Get your head down!
All right, listen. The Terminator's
an infiltration unit...
part man, part machine. Underneath,
it's a hyperalloy combat chassis...
microprocessor controlled,
fully armored, very tough.
But outside, it's
living human tissue.
Flesh, skin, hair, blood...
grown for the cyborgs.
Look, Reese, I don't know
what you want from...
Pay attention! I got
to ditch this car.
The 600 series had rubber
skin. We spotted them easy.
But these are new.
They look human...
Sweat, bad breath, everything.
Very hard to spot.
I had to wait till he moved on
you before I could zero him.
Look... I am not stupid, you know.
They cannot make things like that yet.
Not yet. Not for about forty years.
- Are you saying it's from the future?
- One possible future.
From your point of view...
I don't know tech stuff.
Then you're from the future,
too, is that right?
- Right.
Cyborgs don't feel pain. I do.
Don't do that again.
- Just let me go.
- Listen!
And understand. That
Terminator is out there.
It can't be bargained with.
It can't be reasoned with.
It doesn't feel pity
or remorse or fear.
And it absolutely
will not stop. Ever!
Until you are dead.
Can you stop it?
I don't know.
With these weapons, I don't know.
All units. All units. Gray Ford
suspect vehicle's been found
in a parking structure
at 4th and Beaudry.
Reese.
Why me?
Why does it want me?
There was a nuclear war...
A few years from now.
All this...
This whole place. Everything.
It's gone.
Just gone.
There were survivors.
Here. There.
Nobody even knew who started it.
It was the machines, Sarah.
- I don't understand.
- Defense network computers.
New... powerful...
Hooked into everything.
Trusted to run it all.
They say it got smart...
a new order of intelligence.
Then it saw all people as a threat,
not just the ones on the other side.
Decided our fate in
a microsecond...
extermination.
Did you see this war?
No. I grew up after it...
In the ruins. Starving...
- Hiding from HKs.
- HKs?
Hunter-killers. Patrol machines
built in automated factories.
Most of us were rounded up, put
in camps for orderly disposal.
This was burned in
by laser scanner.
Some of us were
kept alive... to work...
Loading bodies. The disposal
units ran night and day.
We were that close
to going out forever.
But there was one man
who taught us to fight,
to storm the wire of the camps, to smash
those metal motherfuckers into junk.
He turned it around. He brought
us back from the brink.
His name was Connor. John Connor.
Your son, Sarah.
Your unborn son.
Drive!
Reese!
No, Reese! No! No!
No! They'll kill you.
You in the Cadillac!
Let me see your hands now!
Get out of the car!
Drop to your knees!
- Out of the car.
- Drop to the ground.
Sarah...
Sarah, try to drink some of this.
Listen, are you sure it's them? Maybe...
maybe I should look at the bodies.
No. They've been identified,
and there's no doubt.
Oh, God.
God!
Ginger!
Sarah.
- Sarah, this is Dr. Silberman.
- Hi, Sarah.
I want you to tell him
everything that Reese told you.
- Do you feel up to that?
- Yeah. I guess so.
You're a doctor?
- Criminal psychologist.
- Is Reese crazy?
Well, that's what
we're gonna find out.
So, you're a soldier,
fighting for whom?
With the 132nd, under
Perry. From '21 to '27.
- That's the year 2027?
- That's right. And I was assigned...
This is fucking great.
The last two years
under John Connor.
- Who was the enemy again?
- A computer defense system built for...
Oh, damn. Sorry.
Built for SAC-NORAD
by Cyberdine systems.
I see.
And this, uh, computer thinks it can win
by killing the mother of its enemy,
killing him, in effect,
before he's even conceived,
a sort of retroactive abortion?
That guy Silberman cracks me up.
Last week, he had this guy in here that
burned his Afghan. He screwed it first,
- then he set it on fire.
- Hey, shut up.
Why didn't the computer
just kill Connor then?
Why this elaborate scheme
with the Terminator?
It had no choice. Their
defense grid was smashed.
We'd won. Taking out Connor
then would make no difference.
Skynet had to wipe out
his entire existence.
Is that when you captured the lab complex
and found that... uh, what is it called?
Uh... the time
displacement equipment?
That's right. The Terminator
had already gone through.
Connor sent me to intercept,
and they blew the whole place.
How are you supposed get back?
I can't.
Nobody goes home.
Nobody else comes through.
It's just him and me.
Why didn't you bring any weapons,
something more advanced?
Don't you have ray guns?
Ray guns.
Show me a piece of
future technology.
You go naked. Something about the
field generated by a living organism.
- Nothing dead will go.
- Why?
- I didn't build the fucking thing!
- OK, OK. But this...
- Cyborg, if it's metal...
- Surrounded by living tissue!
Oh. Right, right...
This is great stuff. I could
make a career out of this guy.
You see how clever this part is? How
it doesn't require a shred of proof?
And most paranoid delusions are
intricate, but this is brilliant.
Why were the other
two women killed?
Most of the records
were lost in the war.
Skynet knew almost nothing about Connor's
mother. Her full name, where she lived.
They just knew the city. The
Terminator was just being systematic.
- Uh-huh. Well, let's go back to...
- Look, you have heard enough!
I have answered your questions!
Now I have to see Sarah Connor!
- I'm afraid that's not up to me.
- Then why am I talking to you?
- Because I can help you.
- Who is in authority here?
- Reese...
- Shut up!
You still don't get it, do you?
He'll find her.
That's what he does!
That's all he does!
You can't stop him!
He'll wade through you, reach down her
throat, and pull her fucking heart out!
- Doc.
- Let... let go of me!
Sorry.
- So, Reese is crazy?
- In technical terminology...
He's a loon.
Sarah, this is what
they call body armor.
Our TAC guys wear these. It'll
stop a twelve-gauge round.
This other individual must have been wearing
one under his coat. Feel that. Go ahead.
What about when he punched
through the windshield?
He was probably on PCP.
Broke every bone in his hand
and wouldn't feel it for hours.
There was this guy once...
- You see this scar?
- Here.
Thank you.
There's a couch in this other room. Why don't
you stretch out and try to get some sleep?
It'll be at least an hour before your
mother gets here from Big Bear.
- I can't sleep.
- Try.
Well, it may not look it, but
that couch is very comfortable.
You'll be perfectly safe. We got
thirty cops in this building.
Thank you.
- Good night.
I'm a friend of Sarah Connor.
I was told that she's here.
Could I see her, please?
No. You can't see her.
She's making a statement.
- Where is she?
- Look, it may take a while...
if you want to wait, there's
a bench over there.
I'll be back.
What the hell was that?
Gunshot!
- What is it, terrorists?
- Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Stay here.
Let's get out of here!
- Come on! Come on!
- He's got an automatic weapon!
Move it, move it, move it, move it!
What the hell happened
to the lights?
Watch him.
Automatic weapons!
Lock and load! Let's go!
Fire! Fire!
Ed.
Hey!
Sarah!
Reese!
This way.
KFLB news time 4:36.
In the top story of the hour, the
largest single law enforcement
mobilization in California
history is currently underway.
Police in five Southern counties...
are engaged in a massive
manhunt for an unident...
Take this.
All right, let's get
this off the road.
- You cold?
- Freezing.
Reese...
You got a first name?
Kyle.
Kyle... what's it like
when you go through time?
White light.
Pain.
- It's like being born maybe.
- Oh, my God.
I caught one back there.
- You mean you got shot?
- It's not bad.
- We got to get you to a doctor.
- It's OK. Forget it.
What do you mean,
forget it? Are you crazy?
Take this off.
Jesus.
See, it passed right
through the meat.
Oh, this is going to make me puke.
Would you just talk about something?
What?
I don't know. Anything.
Just talk. Tell me about my son.
He's about my height.
He has your eyes.
What's he like?
You trust him. He's got a strength.
I'd die for John Connor.
Well... at least now I know
what to name him.
I don't suppose you
know who the father is,
so I won't tell him to get
lost when I meet him.
John never said much about him.
- I know he dies before the war...
- Wait!
I don't want to know.
So, was it John that sent you here?
I volunteered.
Why?
It was a chance to meet the
legend... Sarah Connor.
Taught her son to fight, organize,
prepare from when he was a kid.
When you were in hiding
before the war...
You're talking about things I
haven't done yet in the past tense.
- It's driving me crazy.
- Aah!
Are you sure you have
the right person?
I'm sure.
Come on. Do I look like
the mother of the future?
I mean, am I tough? Organized?
I can't even balance my checkbook.
Look, Reese, I didn't ask for this
honor, and I don't want it! Any of it!
Your son gave me a message to
give to you. Made me memorize it.
"Thank you, Sarah, for your
courage through the dark years.
I can't help you with what you must soon face
except to say that the future is not set.
You must be stronger than
you imagine you can be.
You must survive, or I will
never exist". That's all.
It's a good field dressing.
You like it? It's my first.
Get some sleep.
It will be light soon.
OK.
Talk to me some more.
About what?
Tell me about where you're from.
All right.
You stay down by day, but at
night you can move around.
You still have to be careful
because the HKs use infrared.
But they're not too bright. John
taught us ways to dust them.
That's when the infiltrators
started to appear.
The Terminators were the
newest... The worst.
Traversing your sector
in search mode.
750 meters north of your position.
Understood. 750 meters north.
Let's go.
Intercept. Over.
There are scavenger teams
in that quadrant.
Avoid contact. Repeat, avoid
contact. We'll get them later.
Roger, echo leader.
- Sector niner, what's your status?
- Situation normal.
Firebase, what's your status? Over.
- Reese. DN384...
- Right. Let him in.
Any infiltrators at
the shopping mall?
No problem. They were clean. We're
cutting short the patrol. Over.
Roger, Yankee-1-7.
You are clear to return.
Terminator! Terminator!
I was dreaming about dogs.
We use them to spot Terminators.
Your world is pretty terrifying.
Hey, buddy, you got a dead
cat in there, or what?
Fuck you, asshole.
Goddamn!
Thank you.
Uh, is this enough?
Yeah, it's enough. I don't
want to ask where you got it.
- I'm coming.
- We need a room.
- All right.
- With a kitchen.
Do you have one with a kitchen?
Mmm.
I am dying for a shower.
We should check your bandage, too.
Later. I'm going out for supplies.
Keep this.
No, I can't tell you where I am,
mom. I was told not to say.
Oh, but, honey, I need to
know where I can reach you.
You tell me to hide out up here at
the cabin like some fugitive and...
and you won't tell me what's
going on? I am worried sick, dear.
OK.
- OK, here's the number. Ready?
- Yes. Go ahead.
It's 408-555...
- 1439.
- Uh-huh.
- Room 9. Got it?
- I've got it.
- I've got to go.
I'm sorry I can't tell you more
right now. I love you, mom.
I love you, too, sweetheart.
- Tiki motel.
- Give me your address there.
What have we got?
Mothballs.
Corn syrup.
Ammonia. What's for dinner?
- Plastique.
- Mmm, that sounds good.
What is it?
Nitroglycerin, basically.
It's a bit more stable.
I learned to make it
when I was a kid.
Make sure there's
none on the threads.
Like this.
Screw the end cap on.
Very gently.
You must've had a fun childhood.
That's good.
All right. Six more like that, and
I'll get started on the fuses.
He'll find us, won't he?
Probably.
It'll never be over, will it?
Look at me. I'm shaking.
Some legend, huh? You must
be pretty disappointed.
No. I'm not.
Kyle...
The women in your time...
what are they like?
Good fighters.
That's not what I meant.
Was there someone special?
- Someone?
- A girl. You know.
No.
Never.
Never?
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
So much pain.
Pain can be controlled.
You just disconnect it.
So you feel nothing?
John Connor gave me a
picture of you once.
I didn't know why at the
time. It was very old...
Torn... faded.
You were young like you are now.
You seemed just... a little sad.
I used to always wonder what you
were thinking at that moment.
I memorized every line,
every curve.
I came across time for you, Sarah.
I love you. I always have.
I shouldn't have said that.
Think fast!
Trade places!
Faster! Drive faster!
Kyle!
Oh, my God!
Kyle.
- Whoa!
- Son of a bitch!
You stay here.
Let's get out of here.
Get out.
Kyle. Come on, get up.
He's coming.
Kyle? Come on!
Help me! Get out! Get out!
Get out!
Come on!
Faster!
Don't stop! Run!
Sarah!
Kyle!
Oh, Kyle. Kyle.
We did it, Kyle. We got it.
No!
Wait!
- What are you doing?
- Cover, so he can't track us.
Come on! Come on. No, Kyle!
- Come on! Come on!
- Leave me here.
Get up!
Move it, Reese!
On your feet, soldier!
On your feet! Move it!
Back. Go back.
- Run, Sarah.
- No.
Run!
Come on, motherfucker.
No, no.
You're terminated, fucker.
Kyle.
6450 Bellingham Avenue, Super
Trader. 6450 Bellingham Avenue.
Tape 7, November 10. Where was I?
What's most difficult for me is trying to
decide what to tell you and what not to.
But I guess I have a while yet before you're
old enough to even understand these tapes.
They're more for me at this point,
just so that I can get it straight.
- Gasolina, por favor.
- ¿Cuánto?
- Llena el tanque.
- Fill her up, sí.
Should I tell you about your
father? Boy, that's a tough one.
Will it affect your decision to send him
here, knowing that he is your father?
If you don't send Kyle,
you can never be.
God, a person could go
crazy thinking about this.
I suppose I will tell you.
I owe him that.
Maybe it'll help if...
You know that in the few
hours that we had together...
We loved a lifetime's worth.
Usted es muy hermosa, señora,
y tengo pena decirle
que me de cinco dolares americanos,
pero si no, mi padre me va a pegar.
- What did he just say?
- He says you're very beautiful, señora...
and he's ashamed to ask you for five
American dollars for his picture,
but if he doesn't, his
father will beat him.
Pretty good hustle, kid.
- Cuatro
- Sí, sí.
Gracias.
¡Miren, miren!
¡Allá! ¡Viene una tormenta!
What did he just say?
He said there's a storm coming in.
I know.